邪魔する奴は倒すだけだ。
Ging?
流星街に巣くったキメラアント ザザン
It was my fault... Because of me, Kite
自らを女王と称し 世界征服をたくらむ
turned into a little girl!
彼女の野望を阻止すべく 立ち上がったのは
I h-heard he was captured by the enemy.
この街を故郷とする 「幻影旅団」だった
Yeah, I was with Kite... Then Kite told me to run away, and Pitou showed up.
他の奴らは？ さぁな まだ楽しんでんじゃねえの？
Kite lost his arm, I was knocked out, and then we trained... Shoot got Kite out of the Ants' nest, but it wasn't Kite...
俺も瞬殺しねえで もっと遊べばよかったぜ。
They did all kinds of horrible things!
直さなくっちゃ
Let's calm down. We should both try to calm down...
獲物をなぶる悪い癖
It was because I insisted...
フフフ…。
Ging is actually flustered. I should have
ハハハハ…！　敵じゃないわね！
Gon. That isn't true.
顔をザバっと洗って 出直してらっしゃいな。 確かに。
He took you along because he believed in you.
あら　意外と素直ね。
He told you to run because he'd
underestimated the enemy.
いい練習台　見つけたよ。
If he hadn't thought you capable, he wouldn't have let you accompany
him, no matter what you'd said.
うっ　うぅ…　あっ。
It was his fault that he misjudged the enemy. But— I know.
フフフ…。
You're also at fault for being too weak!
うっ…。
You should feel responsible. Don't make the same mistake.
うん　防戦一方
And you should apologize to Kite, not to me!
動きも速いし 手足の数も私の倍 何とか隙をつくらせないと
You didn't clearly say if he's dead or alive, but either way, you should apologize!
まただな　間違いないべ
When apologizing to a friend, there's a rule. Do you know it?
消したと思ったら　あのオナゴ
Huh? No, what is it?
また　掃除機を 何もない所から出しただ
You promise to do things differently next time.
物体を自由に出したり 消したりする力があるだか
And you keep that promise, no matter what.
なるほど　奥が深いべ
Uh-huh.
オラの粘着糸にも なかなか引っかからねえし
Okay, get going! Yeah!
このまま逃がすわけには いかねえだ！
Ging?
この技　ケツの穴に かなり負担が　かかるだが！
Can I... talk to you some more later?
行くしかねえべ！
That might be difficult. I'm a busy man...
「ラブシャワー」！
Aren't you his father? How cold can you be?!
うわっ　これ　逃げ場ないかも
You never went to see Gon after he cleared it!
ヌフフ…！
Too bashful or something?
糸を飛ばし続けたおかげで 逃げ場が　なくなってるだ！
All you you, shut up! It's none of your business! You're a jerk, Ging!
ラッキー！
You should apologize to Gon!
ウホ　キャッチしただ！
Promise him you'll act more like a father! Hell, you don't have the right
to say you're his father!
うっ　うん…　ん…。
Make up your minds! You can all screw yourselves!
ウホホ…！　無駄だべ！ 怪力ナンバーワンの ビホーン様でさえ
You should have Leorio punch you again! Yeah, just shut up!
この糸だけは 引きちぎれなかっただ。
Fine, then... I'll be waiting, so get going! How stupid do you think we are?
さて　このまま ザザン様に差し出すだ。
You take him there! Aren't you his father? Okay, fine!
ザザン様 褒めてくださるだかな？
I'll take you all on! If you have a problem with
what I'm doing, bring it on!
軽くなった？　まさか…
You're all against me? Okay!
どうやって抜け出ただ？
Everyone!
うぅ！
Quiet down!
ん？
The election isn't over yet.
そうか。
Yes, I still haven't given up.
服を捨てただか！
A new last chance has appeared!
なるほど
Gon-kun—
素肌をガードしながら 糸の隙間を広げて脱出するのは あのオナゴの力なら可能
Go ahead, then. Due to the circumstances, no one
can leave until the election is over.
糸に絡まった掃除機は
You're in a hurry, aren't you? But this will be the final vote.
脱出後に消して　また出せばいい
Once you vote, you'll be allowed to leave.
しかし！　服を脱いだ今 もう　そのては使えねえだぞ！ そのセリフ　お返しします。
If you tell us your choice right now, everyone here will accept that as a valid vote.
あなたの糸のスピード　捕獲範囲 全て理解しました。 教えないけど　発射直前に ２度　肛門がピクつく癖も
Between myself, Pariston, and Leorio-san, whom do you believe is most
fit to become chairman?
もう捕まりません 近寄らないから。 私とデメちゃんの勝ちです。
I should mention that the
former chairman, Netero, is taking an extended vacation
after defeating the Ant King.
勝つ？　ヌフフ…！
How can you say such a thing?
おめぇさん バカなオナゴだなや！ たった今　逃げ回るって 言ったばっかりだべさ！
If Gon picks Leorio after his dramatic arrival, everyone may get caught up in
the heat of the moment again
近寄らないとは言いましたが 逃げるとは　ひと言も。
and vote for Leorio.
ん？
Chairman? Leorio's running for chairman?
どう違うか証明します デメちゃん！
No! See, some stuff happened...
ギョギョ。 あいつの血を 一滴　残らず　吸い取れ！ ギョギョ！
Gon-kun, you can rely on your gut.
な！ な…　ななな…。
Be true to your heart, and pick one of us.
やめるべ。
Huh?
こ…　こら！　こ…　この！
Isn't Leorio-san your friend?
へな！
Shouldn't you pick him?
ヤバい…　ヤバいべ フラフラして来たべ
Nope, because Leorio wants
to become a doctor, so he can't be chairman!
何とか血を止めねば…　あっ
Of course!
ふんぬっ！
Now I've been completely defeated.
まだ!?
Then let's begin the vote. Oh, sorry.
ここも？　こっちからも？
I'm going with Gon.
あっ　あぁ…　あっ　あぁ！
My vote goes to Pariston.
ふ…　ふさぎきれねえ！
Leorio... I know.
２９か所ほど 裂傷による出血を施しました。
Ging!
各部位の位置関係から
I'm going now!
８本の手足で 全箇所を止血するのは
Yeah.
現在までに確認している情報では 不可能です。 奥の手でもない限り。
Is that all you have to say, you idiot? At least say, "See you later"!
あっ　あぁ…。
Where's your common sense?
あぁ。 あぁ。
Ging's snapped! Someone stop this negligent jerk of a father!
あぁ…。
That's impossible! Zodiacs, don't just stand there
and smile! Do something!
お掃除完了！
I remembered something.
ゲップ。
I'm the one who taught Kite how to use Nen.
ん？ うん。
There's a number that his
Crazy Slots won't bring up unless
あの　粘着性の糸って 出せるんですよね。
If he's still alive, that's probably why.
それを全身に巻けば 出血は止められたのでは？
He would never consider dying in your place.
お互い　バカですね。
So don't mess up your apology.
他の連中も　すでに余裕で観戦 少し遊んだとはいえ
Hello, everyone.
僕だって　決して　もたついていた わけじゃないのに
I am your 13th chairman, Pariston. And I have an important announcement.
５…　いや…　７!? 今　フェイント　何回入れた？
I, Pariston, name Cheadle-san as vice chairman, and resign as chairman.
っていうか　何で　あの体勢から 攻撃しながら跳べ…
I didn't see that coming.
わっ　もう　あんなとこにいる
How long must you make fools of us?!
ハァ…
Come back here!
ハハっ…　考えられない
I didn't become vice chairman because
I wanted to become chairman.
レベルが…　違う！
I just wanted to hinder the chairman.
おっ？　イメチェンか？
When I said silly things to tease him, Netero-san always looked so happy...
敵の糸に　やられました。 何だよ　まさか負け…。 勝ったよ！
I really wanted to play with him some more.
恐らく女王だ。 でも　フェイタン　動き良くないね。
I recommend that you reform the Hunter
Exam and Commandments quickly.
僕は　まだまだ　力不足
Cheadle-san, if the Association becomes
a dull place under your leadership, I'll get serious about toying with you.
うっ！　何こいつ どんどん素早くなる！
Leorio, where's Killua? Huh? Oh, I don't know.
仲間も集まって来やがった！
He isn't answering his phone.
チクショ　役立たずどもめ！ 全員　殺られたのかよ！
It sounds like he was traveling,
looking for a way to save you.
フフっ。
Well, once we contact him,
I'm sure he'll come see you.
お…　おのれ!! よくも私の顔に傷を!!
Why are you apologizing? Well, sorry that I couldn't do anything
when you guys were in trouble. Huh? What do you mean?
うっ　うぅ…！
I don't get it. Yeah, I'm really sorry.
うぅ…。
The requests following a wish for a computer
ハァ…。 うぅ…。
should be more severe than playing
dead and a pat on the head.
ハァ　ハァ…！ ぶっ殺…！
When I heard Milluki's report,
that was the first thing that seemed off.
「硬」！ 全身　隙だらけ これ　見逃すほど 私　お人よしないね
And when the two-choice wish resulted
in a simple kiss on the cheek, it demanded fingernails, a far too heavy price.
はぁ！
Assuming that the fingernails were
the price for the computer, Wish                                            Request that would match the balance between
wishes and requests seen previously.
あっ！　攻撃は当たってないはず。 いや　弱っちぃが オーラを飛ばしてる。
If my theory is correct, playing dead and the pat on the head
weren't requests from Something.
「硬」での攻撃が仇になったな。 オーラを「硬」で 一点集中させたのに
Thus, the two-choice wish didn't require a payment.
ノーダメージってのは フェイタンの想定外。
Why was that the case?
計算違いで「念」のガードが 一瞬　遅れてる。
There are two possibilities. One, because the wish was simple enough
稚拙な放出系攻撃でも 大ダメージを受けたはずだ。
that Something's power wasn't required.
ゴホっ。 オーラの使いどころを よく知ってやがる。
Two, because it wasn't a wish.
だてに女王を名乗ってないね。
However, there's still an unresolved question here.
ハハハ…！ この体に隙なんかないんだよ！
If playing dead and the pat on the head
weren't requests from Something...
助けなくていいの？ はっ？　何で？　競争って言ったろ。
They were requests from Alluka, not Something.
あいつが殺られたら 次の奴が行けばいいんだよ。 次は誰？ 先着順だろ？
Killua claims that Something calls him "Killua,"
じゃあ　俺だ。 待てよ ここに着いたのは　俺と同時だろ？
and the request to play dead was made to "Brother."
バカ　俺は　お前が 戦い終わるのを待ってたんだろが。
Thus, the one who calls Killua "Brother" is Alluka.
こ…　こいつら 絶対　変！ 表。
If the request came from Alluka, then Something wasn't awake, and Killua shouldn't have been
able to make the two-choice wish.
じゃ　フェイタンが殺られたら 次は俺だな。 う。 甘かった
However, Something responded to Killua's wish.
ナンバー２くらいなら すぐとか思ってたけど…
The hint to resolving this contradiction
lies in the wording Killua used.
はるか格下だ
When making the two-choice wish,
Killua was not asking. He was commanding.
絶望的なくらい… でも　諦めない 耐えるのは慣れてる
It makes sense that a command
would work differently than a wish, and would not require a payment upon completion.
何年かかっても 兄さんを取り戻すため
Those are my conclusions. What do you think?
イッたな　左腕。
I'll get to the point.
プッ。
I'm the one who can use Something's power,
effectively and safely, for the Zoldyck family.
ヤベェ　逃げろ。 巻き添え食らうぞ。 あいつ　キレると 周りとか関係なく能力出すから。 前に一度　それ見物しようとして 殺されかけたもんね。
But if I control him with you at his side, at the very least, I can guarantee his freedom.
あいつの能力は範囲が広いし
Brother...
他にも種類があるってこと？
I'll protect Alluka.
クソ　見たい
Kil, you need to learn your place.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
'Kay.
ハァ　ハァ…　はっ！
Kil, this is your last chance.
何!?
Let me have Something—
いや　それよりも　明らかに さっきより強いぞ！
Teleportation...
灼熱に変えて！
That's amazing... He's invincible.
「ペインパッカー」！
If Killua issues a command, there is no need to worry about requests.
ん？ ハァ　ハァ…。
This means that turning Killua into
my puppet is worth any price.
ん？　はっ…
Tsubone, Amane...
「ライジング・サン」！
Can you leave us alone for a moment?
うわ!!
If you don't leave on your own, I'll have to issue Something a command.
ハハハ…！
You can't come out anymore.
ハハハ…！ 女王の…　私が
I love Killua.
こん…　な…　とこ…　ろで…
You can't come out, Something.
ヒャハハハ…！
I love Killua.
I love Killua! You can't! Never come out again!
もう　燃料切れか。
'Kay...
もっと楽に死ねたよ。 まっ　自業自得ね。
Alluka is free now.
やはり女王が死んでも
Brother?
体は　もう 元には戻らねえようだな。
Yep, it's your big—
女王の支配からは 解放されてるみたいだけどね。
Did you make Something cry?
ん？
Huh?
ボ…　レ…。
Er, well... She's still hunched over, crying!
ゴボ…　ズグ。
Apologize to her!
ゴ…　ボ…。 ゴロシ…　デ…　ク…　レ…。
If you're nice to me, you have to
be nice to Something, too!
頼む…
If you're going to protect me,
you have to protect Something, too!
俺達を…。
If you're mean to Something, I'll hate you!
かかって来いよ　クソども。
Alluka, thank you.
おめぇら　腐っても ここの住人だろうが！
I guess I was still under Ill-nii's control.
最期まで根性　見せやがれ!!
But everything's okay now.
じいさん達 今度は報復の対象を
Something, I'm sorry.
本当の女王アリまで広げるか どうかで　もめてやがった。
I was wrong. I'm sorry!
…ったく 付き合いきれねえバカどもだな。
I was scared of Ill-nii, and I couldn't defy him.
テーブル囲んで できもしねえことばっか ピチクパチク さえずりやがって。
So I did what he said, and I hated it.
それでも　ここに残るんでしょ？
When I realized he might force you
だって　他にやることねえしよ。
to do bad things, too, I got really scared...
今度　アリが来たら　即行 始末してやる　二度とあんな 後味の悪ぃ殺しはしねえ。 [TEL] おっ。 団長か？
For Alluka's sake, I lied to myself, and I said mean things to you.
いや　ノブナガだった。
I'm really sorry!
こっちの仕事を 手伝わないかってさ。 チッ　何だよ　誰がやるか　バカ！
Something, I'll protect you. We'll always be together!
ああ　うぜぇ。
Don't listen to wishes from anyone else anymore!
ただ待つ身は　つれぇな。
I'll pat you on the head whenever you want!
フィンクスってば 何か片思いの女のコみたい。
So would you please come out again?
流星街は キメラアントの侵略を免れた
Something, will you forgive me for being a
ちょうど　その頃…
bad big brother?
ゴンとキルアは
'Kay.
王のため 直属護衛軍によって行われる
love Killua.
国民の選別が開始されるまで…
Tsubone, I've rescinded the restriction on Killua.
あと９日
Please let him know.